<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Empires Mod</title><link>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/</link><description>Recent content on Empires Mod</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Empires UE4 Monthly Update - July 2020</title><link>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-july-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-july-2020/</guid><description>Project Update - Roy Awesome Hey Everyone! Another month in the bag for UE4 and we’ve really kicked some butt. We achieved a major milestone this month, we have held multiple playtests! That’s right, we’ve started to be able to play the game and get a general gameplay loop going. We even found a crash while testing!
Your browser does not support the video tag. This is a large milestone because it has a feeling of making this project real.</description></item><item><title>Empires UE4 Monthly Update - June 2020</title><link>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-june-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-june-2020/</guid><description>Project Update - Roy Awesome Our second full month is complete working on the Empires UE4 port. We have made some very appreciable progress toward completing the Minimum Viable milestone, and we will soon be able to check that one off.
June was a bit slower than May, mostly due to many of our team members returning to work and the reality of life during COVID settling in. As a volunteer, free time project, we are at the whims of real life obligations to make progress, and while this month’s update is shorter than last, we still made an insane amount of progress.</description></item><item><title>Empires UE4 Monthly Update - May 2020</title><link>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-may-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hmmdeif.github.io/empiresmod-website/posts/unreal-progress-report-may-2020/</guid><description>Hello Everyone! I am incredibly excited to announce that we are porting Empires to the Unreal Engine! This project has been going on for the better part of the month, and we are making extremely good progress. We have brought together a great team and while we are only working nights and weekends on this project, I hope that you can all see how fast we are progressing and how exciting it is for Empires to have a future on a game engine that lets the game excel.</description></item></channel></rss>